<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-03-31T21:33:50-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/</id><title type="html">Jackson’s Blog</title><subtitle>Home of my thoughts and development updates, you decide which is more interesting.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Say hello to Project Kei</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/kei/dev/2017/03/28/say-hello.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Say hello to Project Kei" /><published>2017-03-28T14:48:03-07:00</published><updated>2017-03-28T14:48:03-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/kei/dev/2017/03/28/say-hello</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/kei/dev/2017/03/28/say-hello.html">&lt;p&gt;This game has been in my head a while, and the only question you should have for me is “Is it going to be good?” Well to me a good game has a sort of essay-ic quality, where it’s making strong and even combative points not only about its own subjects and themes, but about what games are and what they can be, all in a thematically resonant and cohesive way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jacksonlango.com/blog/images/kaneda-header.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Project Kei&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d like this game to reach that point someday, but I’ll admit that right now it’s mostly pretty lights and rain. Kei is the working project name for a cyberpunk experience I’m creating and in it I’m prioritizing the things that make cyberpunk an interesting and important genre to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The guiding principle for this game is “A playground for rebellion.” Every mechanic, every piece of environment generation should reinforce this principle. Cyberpunk draws me in when it’s about rebellion and resistance, especially when it’s desperate and even knowingly futile, and that’s what I want to capture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In gaming terms, this experience will be a rogue-like that pushes the boundaries of that genre. It will draw a lot from the staples and experiments in the genre, and the ASCII aesthetic is the most immediate tell that I have its history on my mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now I’m building the mega-sprawl this game will take place in. I’m also devising the way you can hack through it and generally cause trouble. I hope you’ll follow the development with me as I explore this exciting new dystopia!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This game has been in my head a while, and the only question you should have for me is “Is it going to be good?” Well to me a good game has a sort of essay-ic quality, where it’s making strong and even combative points not only about its own subjects and themes, but about what games are and what they can be, all in a thematically resonant and cohesive way.</summary></entry></feed>